

EKATERINA ABRAMOVICH

DESIGNER

Location:

New York, NY, USA

Phone:

551 344 73-53

Email:

eabramovich68@gmail.com

Website:

https://ekaterina-abramovich.com

ABOUT ME

I am an international Junior-level student majoring in Design & Tech at Parsons School of Design. I have experience in various creative fields, such as graphic design, UI/UX design, web design, game design, animation, and 3D modeling.

EDUCATION

MULTIMEDIA PROGRAMMING AND DESIGN

August 2018 to May 2020

Associate in Science Degree

GPA: 3.7

Borough of Manhattan Community College New York, NY, USA

DESIGN AND TECHNOLOGY

August 2022 to Present

Bachelor of Fine Arts

GPA: 3.9

Parsons School of Design at The New School New York, NY, USA

EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

September 2022 to June 2023

EUGENE LANG COLLEGE, THE NEW SCHOOL - New York

Create promotional materials for college events, websites, digital media platforms, newsletters, and initiatives.

UI/UX DESIGNER

August 2020 to September 2022

INSILICO MEDICINE - Hong Kong

Designed user interfaces for web platforms in collaboration with product managers and front-end developers, gathered and evaluated user requirements, designed the corporate website on Tilda Website Builder, created graphics and presentations.

CONTRACT DESIGNER

May 2020 to August 2020

YAMAGUCHI - Moscow, Russia

Designed the company's website and mobile app, created presentations and graphic materials.

HARD SKILLS

Photoshop	Illustrator	InDesign
Figma	Sketch	After Effects
Adobe XD	Canva	WordPress
HTML/CSS	Unity	Maya